dirtywheel.com 2018-12-16

# Privacy Policy

Welcome to dirtywheel.com. The dirtywheel.com website (the "Site") is comprised of various web pages operated by Dirty Wheel LTD. ("Dirty Wheel"). This Statement of Privacy applies to the dirtywheel.com and Dirty Wheel LTD. and governs data collection and usage. By using the dirtywheel.com, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. Please read this statement carefully, and keep a copy of it for your reference.

**A) Log Files**  
Like many other web sites, dirtywheel.com makes use of log files. These files merely logs visitors to the site - usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, the number of clicks etc. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**B) Cookies and Web Beacons**  
dirtywheel.com may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize dirtywheel.com pages, or register with any Dirty Wheel sites or services, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Dirty Wheel website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Dirty Wheel features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Dirty Wheel services or websites you visit.

**C) Third Party Partners**  
Some of our advertising partners, such as Google, may use cookies and web beacons to serve ads on dirtywheel.com. These cookies and web beacons enable our partners to serve ads to our site's visitors based upon their visit to dirtywheel.com and other sites on the Internet.

The third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on dirtywheel.com and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, Web Beacons etc.) may also be used by our site's third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site.

Dirty Wheel has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. dirtywheel.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

**D) Children's Information**  
We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in and/or monitor and guide their online activity.

dirtywheel.com does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that dirtywheel.com has in its database the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately (using the contact page on the Site) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

If you are under 18, you may use dirtywheel.com only with permission of a parent or guardian.

**E) Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

**F) Changes to This Statement**  
Dirty Wheel will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Dirty Wheel encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Dirty Wheel is protecting your information.

**G) Entire Agreement**

By using dirtywheel.com, you hereby consent to dirtywheel.com's privacy policy and agree to its terms.

Unless otherwise specified herein, these privacy policies, together with dirtywheel.com's Terms and Conditions constitute the entire agreement between the user and Dirty Wheel with respect to the Site and it supersedes all prior or contemporaneous communications and proposals, whether electronic, oral or written, between the user and Dirty Wheel with respect to the Site. A printed version of this agreement and of any notice given in electronic form shall be admissible in judicial or administrative proceedings based upon or relating to this agreement to the same extent an d subject to the same conditions as other business documents and records originally generated and maintained in printed form. It is the express wish to the parties that this agreement and all related documents be written in English.
